and what in Bashkiria, as a
а что у вас в Башкирии как
Tatar, makes Bandera nervous, for example
татарина нервирует Бандера например
Bandera, because they are turning
Бандера потому что они переворачивают
history upside down, they want to turn our
историю они хотят перевернуть нашу
story upside down, let’s say in Ukraine they
историю давайте так допустим в Украине
somehow turned up the story, because of this it is
как-то перевернули историю из-за этого
necessary to bomb Ukraine
надо бомбить Украину
Well, because they are remaking our history,
Ну потому что нашу историю переделывают
yours is Whose our ours  This is a Tatar
вашу это Чью нашу нашу это татарскую
Bashkir
башкирскую
from Russia, I’m asking how you feel about
из России спрашиваю как вы относитесь к
the war in Ukraine about the war in Ukraine
войне в Украине к войне в Украине
Yes, positively
Да положительно А
Why because they are liberating the country
почему потому что они освобождают страну
from the Nazis from the Nazis And you yourself  from which
от нацистов от наци А вы сам из какого
region of Russia I myself
региона России я сам с
understood from the Bashkirs And are you Bashkir or Russian I’m a
башкири понял А вы башкир или русский я
Tatar in general a Tatar Yes that’s good And what is
татарин вообще татарин Да вот хорошо А в
Nazism in
нацизм в
Ukraine Nazism
Украине нацизм
Well, how do you like
Ну как вам ска
it with Nazism is when they support
так с нацизм это когда поддерживают
Bandera that’s what Nazism is So what do you have
бандеру вот в чём нацизм Так а что у вас
in Bashkiria  how the
в Башкирии как
Tatar is unnerved by Bandera, for example
татарина нервирует Бандера например
Bandera, because they are turning
Бандера потому что они переворачивают
history around, they want to turn our
историю они хотят перевернуть нашу
history around, let’s say in Ukraine they
историю давайте так допустим в Украине
somehow turned history upside down, because of this
как-то перевернули историю из-за этого
they need to bomb
надо бомбить
Ukraine because our history
Украину потому что наш историю
is being remade,
переделывают
our our is the Tatar head, this is
ью нашу нашу это татарскую башки этоже
also ours Well, history and yours
это же и наша Ну история и ваша
Wait for what our grandfathers fought for
Подождите за что наши деды боролись
understand Wait that is, Tatar
понима Подождите то есть Татарская
history and Ukrainian history are not
история и украинская история не
Tatar you don’t take a defined well
татарская ты не бери определён ну
nationality You take Russians wait
национальность Ты бери русских подожди
Russian this  same nationality Well, are you
русский это же национальность Ну вы
Tatar or
татарин или
Russian, you know in Russia there are many
русский вы знаете в России есть много
nationalities, if you are in Russia
национальной если ты находишься в России
you are definitely becoming Russian
это ты определённо русским становишься
you understand how it is, well, like this, well,
понимаешь как это ну вот так вот ну
certain nations Well, certain nations,
определённые нации Ну определённые нации
for example, but this is already explained internally
например но это уже внутри разъясняется
as if in how it is if you are you, you are a Yakut
как бы в как это если ты ты вот ты якут
or a Tatar or a Bashkir or a Buryat, but you
или татарин или башкир или бурят но ты
become Russian Because you are in Russia, like
стаёт русским Потому что ты в России как
this, well, gradually you  you become Russian
это ну постепенно ты становишься русским
Because you are in Russia Well, for
Потому что ты находишься в России Ну как
example, if, for example, a person from Africa
Например если например человек из Африки
comes, you
приедет
know, you know, look, please,
это знаете знаете смотрите пожалуйста
what event is happening, for example,
вот происходит какой событие например да
yes, definitely what event But
вот определенно Какое событие Но
no matter what the scale of people
неважно какого масштаба там людей
died there Yes, for example
погибло Да например
they say people from
говорят людей из
Russia from
России из
RO
ро
from they lived in Russia They are Russians Well,
из они жили в России Они россияне Ну ну
of course, they don’t betray, as
да естественно же они же не предают как
if yes, for example, they don’t attach importance,
бы да вот например не придают значению
for example, what kind of national he was Well
например какой он был Националь Ну
look, that is, you are Tatars, you are Russian, but
смотри То есть вы татари вы россиянин но
you are not Russian, these are different things  I'm
вы не русский это разные вещи я я на
actually a Tatar Well, you're not Russian I'm
самом деле татарин Да ну вы не русский Я
not Russian Well, why? You say
не русский Ну да почему же Говорите
Russian history, why do I live in Russia?
русская история по что я в России живу я
I live in Russia because I'm considered
Я живу в России потому что Я считаюсь
Russian for someone I'm considered  Russian
русским для кого-то Я считаюсь русским
as Russian, you are Russian and not Russian,
как русским вы россиянин а не русский
everyone who lives in Russia is
есть вот все кто живут в России это
Russians, that is, Russia Yes, you are
россияне то есть Россия Да вы
right, I am Russian Yes, Russian Tatars live in Russia,
правы я россиянин Да вот в России живут
Yakuts and Bashki, you are Russians,
русские татары якут и башки вы россияне
and what does our
да то какое отношение например наша
history of Ukraine, for example, have to do with Russian
история Украины имеет к россиянкой
history? So  you helped us in the Second
истории Так вы же нам помогали во второй
World War and
мировой и
we need to be bombed, they fought for you
нас это надо бомбить ити воевали за вас
quietly, mom, defended once again Well, now we need to be
тихо мам защ ещ раз Ну и нас теперь надо
bombed like Hitler bombed, we are not bombing
бомбить как Гитлер бомбил мы бомбим не
you
вас а кого Америку и не бомбили вообще
and who America wasn’t bombed at all like your nationalists, look here in Ukraine Kyiv was shelled Kharkov Mariupol was razed to the ground This is not our country this is not ours this is all fake Azov this is being done on purpose so that they think about us poorly you understand yes this is our own this is our own they are shelling our cities, we are actually very friendly people, you understand, no, but wait, that is, uh, Ukraine itself dropped bombs on Mariupol from Russian planes I don’t know  I I I I can’t say I understand this
знаю я я я не могу это утверждать
Because I’m not strong in politics
понимать Потому что я в политике не
I say right away I see that my mother is
силён Сразу говорю я там вижу что мама
strong Yes my mother tells me that
сильна Да мама подсказывает что там
America is bombing there yes Yes but how did you know that
Америка бомбит да Да а как вы узнали что
it’s my Mother You told her You
это Матушка моя Вы же сказали Вы к ней
told her mom to be quieter huh  Well, yes, mom, keep it down,
сказали мама потише а ну да мам потише
look, this is how it turns out, that
давай вот смотрите так получается то
is, Russian troops entered Ukraine,
есть российские войска вошли в Украину
but they are not the ones firing at them, the Ukrainians themselves are firing at
но обстреливают не они обстреливают сами
themselves, so if ours didn’t start,
украинцы себя так если наши не начали бы
yours started, you know, that’s who is doing
ваши начали знаете вот кто делает
normal, that’s what a normal guy
нормально вот какой нормальный мужик
is defending himself with his  alive,
защищается своим живым себя
here's Who does this, here's a normal
вот Кто так делает вот нормальный
guy, and
мужик а
who's behind Here's who is a civilian defending himself,
кто за Вот кто мирными жителя защищается
Russia, for example,
Россия например
Good Look, mother there is even in
Хорош Вот смотрите матушка там даже в
shock, yes, look, for example, Russia is
шоке да вот смотрите например Россия
defending itself with a human shield You were
защищается живым щитом живым щитом вы
defending yourself with a human shield This is what kind of Soldiers are like that, for
защищались Это что за Солдаты такие вот
example, look at the Russian Voight
например смотрите российские Войт
outside  they are a human
вне тся живым
shield no in any case how come they are
щитом нет ни в коем случае как так они
standing in the city in no case there
же стоят в городе ни в коем случае там
is no one there anymore, that is, there is no one in Kherson,
никого уже нету то есть в Херсоне никого
yes no no no, that is, there are no people,
нет да нет нет нет то есть людей нет
only your troops  Yes, they are standing in Kherson, and
только ваши войска стоят Да в Херсоне а
they did everything possible
они всё возможно сделали
so that women and children would not suffer,
чтобы не пострадали бы женщины и
it was you who created everything for
детей это вы это вы всё создали сами
yourself, but look, let’s
себе е а вот смотрите Давайте ещё раз
look at it like this again when Hitler is
так смотрите когда Гитлер Гитлер же
bad, why did the
плохой та
Soviet troops stand in
ня Почему советские войска стояли в
Stalingrad, would have fought well  Yes,
Сталинграде бы воевал хорошо Да вот
look Why did Soviet troops stand
смотрите Почему советские войска стояли
in Moscow in Leningrad in
в Москве в Ленинграде в
Stalingrad Ukraine defended good you are
Сталинграде Украину защищали хорош ты ты
leading me into pathology
меня с патологии сбиваешь
you can always shut up
постоянно може замолчать
[music]
[музыка]
stand in cities A  Ukrainians are not allowed,
стоять в городах А украинским нельзя
but you know what, yes, how do you generally treat Russia
да Вы как вообще относитесь к России
badly because it attacked my
плохо потому что она напала на мою
country? This is not this, this is not
страну Это не это не
an attack, this is
нападение это
a special operation, whatever you call it,
спецоперация как Как бы вы не называете
But this is an attack on Ukraine. Is it
Но это есть нападение на Украину Да
good already? You don’t know anything, I’m
хорош ли уже Ты же ничего не знаешь я
still  you don’t know, I know everything, it’s already
всё это ты не знаешь я я-то всё знаю уже
impossible for the Armed Forces to know, damn it,
получается невозможно ВС знать блин
we didn’t bring troops into Russia, but
вывели не мы ввели войска в Россию а
we brought troops into Ukraine, called it
вывели в Украину войска назвал это
a special operation, don’t touch
спецоперацию так не трогайте там
mom there Hello hello, I’m here Dava father-in-law
маму Алло алло я здесь Дава тесть
swears Well, let's talk to her about it on the air
материт А ну давайте если что её в эфир
now, we'll talk to her, yes If she
сейчас мы с ней поговорим да Если она
wants to speak out so much Well, come on Our mother
так хочет высказаться Ну давай Мам наши
protects
защищает
yours, let's talk to you eye to
ваши да давайте поговорим с вами глаза в
eye, she doesn't want to, why then yes If you
глаза она не хочет зачем тогда да Если
don't want to, yes the lady protects you so that
не хотите да госпожа вас защищает чтобы
you can live  it’s normal so that you
вы жили нормально чтоб благополучно
understand safely, we ask you to come to us and so we live
понимаете мы просим лез к нам мы и так
safely
жим благополучно
already a hundred Ukrainians are there NATO, you understand
уже стот украинские там НАТО понимаете
No, they have bacteriological laboratories,
Нет они лаборатории бактериологические
laboratories have already built everything there, you
лаборатории там уже вс построили
understand these are diseases they spread,
понимаете это болезни они распространяют
you don’t understand this And what diseases do
вы этого не понимаете А какие болезни у
we have?  distributed, kept as living
нас распространили держат как живые
accounts for them,
счета для них
you understand for America, America
понимаете для Америки Америка
someday had to
когда-нибудь всё равно должен был
attack anyway, so
напасть вот и он вас
in short, he supplies you, supplies you with nothing else,
короче снабжает снабжает больше ничего
he won’t give you anything, and for this weapon, he
он не даст вам а за это оружие Он с вас
’ll still demand three times more from you, everything
ещё будет требовать три раза больше всё
x good A  look, you
х расп хорошо А смотрите вот голод
'll be starving soon you're Tatars so the
будете сидеть скоро вы вы татары так
Russians once captured the Tatars you
русские когда-то захватили татар вы
Kazan was like this Well it was yes yes it
Казань было такое А ну это было да да
was yes that is, it turns out you live under
было да то есть получается вы живёте под
Russian occupation now so no yes
оккупацией русских сейчас так нет да у
you don't have your own  states of Tatarstan
вас нет своего государства Татарстана
If only, look, if
Вот если бы смотри если бы под
we lived under occupation, we wouldn’t live like that, they would
оккупацией мы жили бы мы так не жили
exterminate us and kill us, they would just
бы истребили бы нас да убили бы просто
kill us and that’s it. But no, they united all the
убили бы и всё А нет они соединили все
nations. Yes, just look. Why Tatarstan?
нации Да так смотрите А почему Татарстан
Why do you have Tatarstan? Here it is on the
Почему у вас Татарстан Вот он в дено
second day  year you had a referendum about the
втором году у вас был референдум так про
independence of Tatarstan, we had such
независимость Татарстана было такое у
independence of Bashkiria, it also happens in a
нас независимость Башкирии тоже бывает
friendly way, you understand, these are not the same
это дружественно понимаете не такими это
conditions. How do you
условиями Как у вас вы детей
raise your children as nationalists? You understand, no,
воспитываете националисты понимаете нене
why?  why don’t they let you become a
А почему почему вам не дают стать
separate state so that you can
отдельным государством чтобы вы себе
live and develop your own language and
жили развивались свой язык
honor Yes, but we have our own language, yes And in
чтили Да но у нас есть свой язык да А в
schools Let’s teach in your schools
школах Давайте в школах у вас обучение
what language is taught in the Russian
на каком языке идёт на башки на русском
language Bashkir is also not Bashkir, they
языке башкирский тоже не башкирский
just study but there is mathematics  in
просто изучают но там математику на
which
каком
Yes good is good not math you
Да хорош хорош нере математику вы на
study in Russian in Russian in Russian
русском изучаете на русском на русском
Yes why not in Bashkir in
Да а почему не на башкирском на
Bashkir We have a Bashkir
башкирско У нас есть башкирский
language you will calm down  or that No, they don’t
язык ты успокоишься или что Нет они не
just misunderstand us, you
просто неправильно понимают нас
understand, it just turns out they let you
понимаешь просто получается вам дают там
study there at school, how many lessons there are in the
в школе изучать там сколько там уроков
Bashkir language, but mathematics, all
башкирский язык но математика все
subjects are taught in
предметы идут на русском
Russian Why do the Russians let you study in
языке Почему русские дают вам учиться на
your language?
вашем языке
They don’t let you study in your
Они они не дают учиться вам на вашем
language, they  they impose the Russian language on this And
языке они навязывают русский язык это А
why is the most important language is Russian
почему самый главный язык - это русский
Why is the most important language Russian?
Почему самый главный язык русский Потому
Because Russia bro Well that's right Why
что Россия братан Ну правильно А почему
don't they let you study in your language We
вам не дают учиться на вашем языке Мы
study in our own language only we have
учимся на своём языке только у нас есть
separate circles separate these I
отдельные кружки отдельные эти я
separate circles  of your language, yes, that is,
отдельные кружки вашего языка да то есть
as you know, there are some, that is, why
как знаете там какие-то то есть А почему
don’t you teach the basic subjects in your
не не учите основные предметы на вашем
language, physics,
языке физику
chemistry, if everyone needs to be taught, well, you know
химию если всех надо учи ну вы знаете
why you know
почему знаете почему
why the majority is composed in Russian,
почему большинство слагается на русский
everything is composed in Russian,
язык всё всё слагается на русский язык
here you have it  what is the main language Ukrainian is
вот у вас какой язык основной украинский
good already Good already Calm down No I’m
хорош уже Хорош уже Успокойся Нет я
just
просто
saying the majority of
говорю большинство
these
этих
researchers scientists as if yes they were
исследователей учёных как бы да они были
Well from
Ну с
Russia you knew in the world scientists
россие вы знали в мировых учёных
the majority were from
большинство было с
Russia where you read that I’m
России где вы такое прочитали мне
interested and everyone goes to  USA everyone goes to the
интересно и все идут в США все идут в
USA because we don’t pay enough for it.
США потому что у нас мало платт за это А
Why
почему
go to Ameri dollar de
поход в Амери долла де
to America that’s why they live well
в Америку они поэтому они хорошо живут
Wait, so it turns out that your money is
Подождите То есть получается ваши деньги
now going to America Yes, they left before that,
сейчас уходят в Америку Да ушли до этого
yes, that is, that is, you are controlled by
да то есть то есть вами вами управляет
America  that's right And now, well, to some
Америка правильно А сейчас ну в какой-то
extent, yes, yes, that is, he has now
степени да да то есть он сейчас все
blocked all our accounts. Wait,
заблокировал все наши счета Подождите то
why did you attack us? If you are
почему вы напали на нас Если вами
controlled by
управляет
America, you know this, this is in
Америка это знаете это это это в
the humanitarian, this is not your war, this is
гуманитарной это не ваша война это
America, the war is not that humanitarian, that
Америка война не что гуманитарный что
humanitarian humanitarian I
гуманитарный гуманитарный имеется в виду
mean about goods all the things here are all the
насчёт товаров все дела вот это вот все
things I don’t understand again That is, if you are
дела Не понял ещё раз То есть если вами
controlled by America, they didn’t
управляет Америка не у до этого
rule you before because
управляла до этого потому что газ по
they bought gas cheaply They have
дешёвке они покупали Они до такой
already updated it to such an extent Pain Pain remember
степени Обновили уже Боль Боль помните
how it has increased  oil because of our Russia
как это возросла нефть изза нашей России
they lived ho stop stop
они жили хо стоп стоп подождите
wait wait I understand correctly that you
подождите я правильно понимаю что у вас
have enormous resources but these resources
есть огромные ресурсы так но эти ресурсы
were taken by Putin and given to America
забирал Путин и отдавал Америке Да
Why did Putin take them they are worldwide
почему забирал Путин они это всемирно
this is how America was still in charge
это како все же руководил
how how America took your oil
Америка как как вот вашу нефть забирала
Tell America they sold
Америка Расскажите Америку продавали
America in short these dollars in short these
Америка короче доллары эти короче по
were bought by a girl because of this
девке покупал изза этого
and who forbade you to sell She
а кто вам запрещал продавать Она имеет в
means before this before this before this Yes how is
виду до этого до этого до этого Да как
it that you have your
как получается вот у вас есть ваши
rulers so Why do they
правители так А почему они по дешёвке
they sell oil cheaply Ani is more expensive there
продают нефть Ани там подороже потому
because America
что Америка так
demanded it America wanted it so we we
требовала Америка хотела так мы мы же
owe America even during the Second World War they
Америке должны ещё за Вторую Мировую
were still
были ещ
working Pain Painfully You can tolerate
абот Боль Боль ско Можно терпеть
for whom no one to no one And you are living bills
для кого никого никому А вы живые счета
for them Why are they  they don’t accept you,
для них Почему они вас не принимают
wait, I just, I just can’t
подождите я просто я просто не могу
understand, you have such a rich country, you all
понять у вас такая богатая страна вы все
will have a rich country in the future.
у нас будет богатая страна дальше
Everything will be fine with us.
Вот у нас всё будет
Russia, we will have a ruble now;
хорошо Россия у нас рубля сейчас будет у
the name of
правильно я правильно Говорите имя
Allah Russia will be
Аллаха Россия будет
uh rich And
ээ богатой А
now the glory of Russia Maybe maybe be
сейчас слава России Может может
silent for a little bit But at least let me
помолчать немножко А хотя бы дай мне
talk a little with the man Auger
поговорить немножко с человеком оже
on purpose so I know I know it perfectly well
специально так я знаю я прекрасно знаю
he knows perfectly well what about but he
это он прекрасно знает что о а вот он
got you emotional Yes  Moreover, I do
тебя на эмоции вывел Да причём Причём я
n’t know very well for me the discovery that
не прекрасно знаю для меня открытие что
America is taking away your resources there. I
Америка там забирают у вас ресурсы Я
think that it’s your oligarchs who are taking
думаю что это ваши олигархи забирают
resources for themselves, our money, oligarchs.
ресурсы себе наши деньги олигархи Боже
My God, my mother is old, just
мой у меня матушка старая просто просто
look, Putin has a palace,
смотрите вот у Путина есть дворец дворец
everyone has a palace, oh  why
есть у всех есть дворец о А почему Путин
did Putin build himself a palace instead of
построил себе дворец вместо того чтобы
giving your mother
отдать вашей маме пенсии
more pensions? Well, our pension is now increasing.
больше ну у нас сейчас возрастает пенсия
What kind of pension do you get from you? Look,
А вы какую пенсию получаете у вас Смотри
I don’t know, I’m not a pensioner, just look at
я не знаю я не пенсионер просто смотри у
us  the president doesn’t have a palace, but we
нас нету дворца у президента вот у нас
don’t have Zelensky building a palace for himself,
нет чтобы Зеленский построил себе дворец
so that is, it turns out like this palace.
так то есть получается вот такой дворец
I watched Navalny’s investigation about
Я смотрел расследование Навального про
this palace in Gelendzhik, how much
вот этот дворец в Геленджике сколько
money could you give to people, so for
можно было раздать людям денег так на
some, build a school, there’s a kindergarten, a
какие-то построить школу Там садик
road, or raise a pension So  why
дорогу или пенсию поднять Так почему
Putin then if he is so good He
Путин тогда если он такой хороший Он
takes money from oil, gas and gold for
забирает деньги из нефти газа и золота
himself And for his friends, you talk like this
себе И своим друзьям вот вы вы так
Yes, if someone came
рассуждаете Да если кто-нибудь пришёл
If you were in his place, how would you
Если вы были бы на место его как вы
look at it, you would also steal
смотрели бы на это тоже также воровали
like Putin so that is, it turns out that
как Путин так то есть то получается то
Putin steals Yes and I would steal too So what do
Путин ворует Да и я бы тоже воровал Так
you think Yes everything is possible What do
а как вы думаете Да всё возможно А как
you think I understand that is look and
вы думаете я понял то есть смотри а
now let’s say Putin
теперь давайте то есть Путин вас
is stealing from you but you support
обворовывает но вы поддерживаете
the attack on Ukraine we are not talking  that I
нападение на Украину мы не говорим что я
didn’t tell you that all the presidents all of
не говорила так вам все президенты все
these all live the way they want and
эти все живут так как хотят так и живут
let’s live like this Putin
давайте так Путин
steals no no no no no matter Where did
ворует нет нет нет нет во тыж А откуда у
he get the palace How do you not know her or
него дворец Как вы же её не знаете илите
wait please Please
подожди пожалуйста Пожалуйста
wait how  I’ll tell you On the air
подожди как я тебе скажу В прямом эфире
that he’s stealing And I got it I got it Okay, yeah, that’s
что он ворует А понял понял О'кей да то
just how I’ll tell you that he’s that
есть он просто как я тебе скажу что он
he’s that they’re all thieves They’re they’re
он что это они все воры Они они Нас
listening to us it’s on Libos Yes it’s just
прослушивают это по либос Да это просто
that’s how Ukraine differs from Russia we
вот чем отличается Украина от России мы
we can talk about our presidents
можем про своих президентов говорить
at least live, even if not live,
хоть в прямом эфире хоть не в прямом
okay, I’ll smoke now. Yes, let’s give it
ладно я Сейчас покурю Вы да Давайте ещё
a couple more minutes. I’ll run too. So yeah, it
пару минут Я тоже уже побегу Так что да
just turns out, look,
договори просто получается смотрите что
I want to understand why Russian Russians
я хочу понять почему русские россияне
support the war in Ukraine, that is
поддерживают войну в Украине так то есть
it turns out there is a war in Ukraine, I know,
получается войну в Украине я знаете
wait please Ma, it just
подожди пожалуйста Ма просто получается
turns out that there are oligarchs there, there are
получается что там олигархи там
presidents, they are pulling resources for themselves And
президенты они тянут себе ресурсы А
why are you attacking
надае вы на
us We didn’t attack you, this is
нас Мы не нападали на вас это
a special operation Well, they attacked in the form of a
спецоперация Ну напали в виде
special operation
спецоперации
naoli that
наоли то
is, that is, you cannot eliminate the
есть то есть вы не можете устранить у
oligarchs in your country  who steal you And
себя олигархов которые вас воруют И
send troops to a foreign country
посылаете войска в чужую страну
to eliminate some nationalists There
устранять каких-то Там националистов А
But you were a nationalist in Ukraine,
вот вы в Украине были
you were in Ukraine No,
националистом вы были в Украине Нет
never happened, that is, you didn’t see
никогда не было То есть не видели там
these there  nationalists And besides Russia, where else
этих националистов А кроме России где ещ
were there Well, I was Nare
были Ну я был Наре
This is how it is in Russia This is in Russia and besides
Это в России так Это в России а кроме
Russia where we were in Murmansk Apart from Russia, in
России где были в Мурманске Кроме России
my opinion, there was nowhere And why For example,
по-моему нигде не было А почему Например
why weren’t we there in Europe in Ukraine well
почему не были там в Европе в Украине ну
because I have a job  doesn’t allow
потому что у меня работа не позволяет
Uh-huh That is, it turns out that you
Угу То есть получается что смотрите Вы
live in such a rich
живёте в такой богатой
country, your oligarchs are so rich in resources, they
стране Так богаты ресурсами у ваших
have yachts. They travel around
олигархов есть яхты Они катаются по
different countries, so the rulers have
разным странам так у правителей есть
palaces, and you don’t even have the opportunity to
дворцы А у вас нет возможности даже
go to another  it will work out because I
съездить в другую получатся потому что я
myself don’t want to. Well, when there’s no opportunity,
сам не хочу А ну когда нет возможности
then I don’t want to either. Yes, for example,
тогда я тоже не хочу Да вот например
Why do I have the opportunity
Почему у меня есть возможность потому
because you, too, also need to have your stomach repaired,
что вас тоже также живот надо ремонт
do all the work there, yes, yes, you see, and then
делать все дела там да да Видите а там
someone in the Palace will get repairs done for  your
кому-то в Дворце сделают ремонт за ваши
money Yes And you won’t go, you already
деньги Да А вы не поедете уже это уже
know that already It’s also the
знаете Это уже у вас тоже также везде
same story everywhere, not only we don’t So
такая же история не только у нас не Так
wait Yes, we are fighting with our
подождите Да так мы со своими боремся
thieves, they are interfering in a foreign country something
ворами они лезем в чужую страну что-то
There to free you, you know why ours
Там вас освобождать знаете почему наши
started  spice for you  because on March 8 it
начали вам специа потому что 8 марта уже
was already known you weren’t supposed to
было известно вы на должны были это
attack Crimea on March 8 you understand so
нападать в Крым 8 марта понимаете чтобы
that this doesn’t happen ours faster so that
вот это не случилось наше быстрее чтобы
you are blocked in short wait don’t
вас короче заблокировали подождите не
wait your your this president said
Подождите ваш ваш этот президент сказал
that we are carrying out denazification and demilitarization here,
что это мы проводим тут денацификация и
that is  you won’t come up with the idea
есть-то То есть вы не придумаете про то
that Ukraine wanted to attack, your president
что Украина хотела напасть ваш президент
can’t lie, it’s true. Why do you
не может обманывать правда А почему вы
allow, for example, America? Yes, they
позволяете например в Америку Да возле
are building
вашей границы строят Там
biological laboratories near your border. Look, even if
биолаборатории смотрите даже если бы у
we had  biolaboratories America these are our
нас были биолаборатории Америка это наши
personal problems, what do we want here and
личные проблемы что мы хотим тут и А
why do they spread all sorts of
зачем они распространяют всякие там
diseases there? What diseases do they
болезни ка Какие болезни они
spread, infected
распространяют заразили
everyone or infected with smallpox, everything is possible there. What if, well, everything is
всех или заражённых оспой там у вас всё
possible, yes Then look, then it’s possible like
возможно да Тогда смотрите тогда можно
this, did you imagine that  Russia
так а вы вы представляли что Россия у
in Bashkiria in
вас в Башкирии в
Bashkortostan Also has secret
Башкортостане Тоже имеет секретные
biological laboratories, it’s possible, we
биолаборатории это же возможно знаем
know, we know, we know, so Why are
знаем знаем знаем так Почему ж вы не
n’t you fighting against them, but
против них не боретесь а против
fighting against the Ukrainians because  that there is no time
украинских боретесь потому что некогда
Well, I mean, They are ours Well, how are they
Ну в смысле Они же наши Ну как они
against their own and this is in America, it’s
против своих а это у вас в Америке это
all blocked there by America,
всё у вас заблокировал там Америка ва
look if America is so bad Why do
смотри если Америка такая плохая Почему
people in America live better than people in
люди в Америке живут лучше чем люди в
Russia they live on our money on our
России они на наши деньги живут на наши
dollars  Well, it just turns out,
доллары Ну как Просто получается вот
look, we lived, I was born back in the
смотрите мы жили вот я родился ещё в
Soviet Union, so people in America lived
Советском Союзе так люди в Америке жили
better than people in the Soviet Union and everyone
лучше чем люди в Советском Союзе и все
wanted to escape to America. But not And they lived on our
хотели убежать в Америку Но не А на наши
money as they did
деньги жили как они
when our rubles turned into dollars. So
де дола наши рубли превращали доллар Вот
they lived  owners with  everyone, she
они жили хозяины со всех она плохо
speaks Russian poorly, it’s
говорит по-русски
just normal,
просто нормально
since you speak
раз Ты плохо говоришь
Russian poorly, speak normally
по-русски нормально говори
Porus see with your mother then
Порус видите с мамой потом
discuss dada
подискутировать
yes, I also asked this question
дада да я тоже задавался этим вопросом
Okay, let’s do it Glory to Ukraine, subscribe
Ладно всё давай Слава Украине подпишись
to my Telegram directly at once ovin and
на мий Telegram прямо зараз овин а
pok tse more and more respectfully  YouTube is
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through SR Georgi into a shadow ban
загоняя нас через СР георги в теней бан
and a lot more video I don’t show people
и дуже багато вдео не показую людям
at the moment I don’t show information  about streams
вчасно не показуе информация про стримы
for this purpose so that we Mali operational
тому для того щоб мы Мали оперативный
link write directly at the same time and while there in
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegra okm video also tezh Tsikava and Korisna
телегра окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry for you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Украине подпишись